那么你今天是如何去上班的呢？
So how did you get to work today?
我有一辆自行车  挺不错的
&gt;&gt; I have a bike, works out just fine.
你呢？
How about you?
好吧  我开车去的
&gt;&gt; Okay. I drive.
酷！  你的车怎么样？
&gt;&gt; Oh cool, how's that car working out?
挺不错的
&gt;&gt; It's good.
是吗  那你知道它是如何工作的吗
&gt;&gt; Yeah? Do you know how it works,
引擎盖下的秘密是什么呢？
underneath the hood?
不  我不需要知道
&gt;&gt; No, I don't need to.
我只需要插入钥匙  然后直接启动就行
I just need to put the key in, and then I drive it.
你知道  这就好像写代码一样
You know, this is kind of like writing code.
哪些方面像呢？
&gt;&gt; In what way?
嗯。。。  其实都很像写代码
&gt;&gt; Well, everything is kind of like writing code.
对的  别走神  听我好好解释
&gt;&gt; Okay, yeah. &gt;&gt; Stick with me for a second.
在之前的课程里  我们给学生们一大堆代码
In previous lessons we gave students a bunch of code.
我们为他们提供了一些调用方法  比如显示方法
&gt;&gt; Yeah. We gave them methods like the display
显示价格方法
method and the display price method.
对的  而且我们一直在说
&gt;&gt; Right. And we kept saying,
别担心这个
well, don't worry about this.
我们以后会详细解释它们的功能
We'll talk about what it does later.
所谓的"以后"就是现在
Well that later is now.
好吧好吧
&gt;&gt; Okay. &gt;&gt; Okay.
正如你知道汽车是如何工作的一样
So much like you know how a car works.
你可以使用这些方法
You can use it.
学生们可以利用这些方法
Students were able to use that method.
是吗？
&gt;&gt; Okay. &gt;&gt; Right?
但是我们设计了这个方法  所以这里
But we wrote the method, so we were
我们就相当于汽车的设计师  我明白了
the designers of the car in that case. &gt;&gt; I see.
所以主题思想就是你可以在其他地方定义方法
So the main idea is that you can define the method somewhere.
就好像造车一样
&gt;&gt; So that's like building the car.
然后在后面你可以调用那个方法
&gt;&gt; And then later you can call that method.
相当于开车
&gt;&gt; That's like driving the car.
对
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
后面我们还要用到这个思想
&gt;&gt; So let's use those ideas next.
听起来不错
&gt;&gt; Sounds good.
在MainActivity.java文件里
&gt;&gt; Within the MainActivity.java file,
display 方法就在这定义
this is where the display method is defined.
这里是它被调用的地方  在increment方法里
And this is where it's getting called, within the increment method and
和decrement方法
within the decrement method.
display方法的实现体接受一个数字的参数
The instructions of the display method take in a number and
然后在屏幕显示
then display it on the screen.
就像这里一样
Like this right here.
我们可以将它的实现体拷贝到调用该方法的地方
Instead of defining a method we can also just take the instructions inside of it
而不是重新定义一个新的方法
by copying it and then pasting it where we called that method.
由于数字在这里不是变量  我们将仅仅改变它的数量
And since number is not a variable here, we're going to change it to quantity.
如果我们想要实现increment方法
If we want to do the same for
一样的功能  可以将代码拷贝到这里
the increment method, we'd copy this code and then paste it up here.
这段代码和我们之前那段的功能一样
So this code works the same as we had before, but
现在我们不需要display方法
now we don't need the display method.
不过这样的实现方法的弊端是我们在两个方法里出现了
The disadvantage to this implementation is that we have duplicate code
冗余的代码
in both methods.
相反  如果我们定义display方法  然后以这个名字调用它
Instead, if we define the display method and then we just call it by its name,
然后我们就可以精简代码  这对程序是好的
then we can have less code which is better for the app.
我还要给大家展示一下其它很酷的东西
I also want to show you something else that's cool.
每当你看到一个方法  你可以点一下然后再右键点一下
Anytime you see a method, you can click on it and then right click.
然后转向"声明"  如果用的是Mac  可以使用Command + V快捷键
And then go to declaration, or Command + V if you're on a Mac.
这样会转向我们定义函数方法的地方
This scrolls the file to where the method is defined.
这个很有用  通过它你可以看到函数方法的
This is useful because then you can see the actual instructions that
实现体
are contained within that method.
对于其它方法
For other methods,
它会打开Android框架代码
it may open up a declaration in the Android framework code.
这些是Android团队写的  比如TextView.java文件
This was written by the Android team, the TextView.java file.
虽然这看起来十分神奇
This shows that, even though things may look like magic,
你可以随时转向该函数方法的代码实现
you can always trace it back to the lines of code where it was defined.
不管是你还是Android团队
Either by you or by someone on the Android team.
为了帮助大家理解方法定义和方法调用之间的区别
To help you understand the difference between defining versus calling
我们来改改MainActivity
a method, let's modify the main activity.
这里我们要改变函数方法定义的方法  将方法的名字从display
We're going to change the way a method is defined by changing the name of
改为displayQuantity
the display method to the name displayQuantity.
对于函数方法的调用  我们需要改变那些代码呢？
Then for calling this method, do we need to change anything about that code?
如果这些改变造成了程序的错误  确保能够定位到错误
If these changes cause an error in your app, make sure to address that so
然后再在设备上重新运行一遍
that you can run the app on your phone again.
完成后在方格里打勾
Check these boxes when you're done.